[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the only congressman to vote against going to war against Japan on December 8, 1941?", "correct_answer": "Rankin", "incorrect_answers": ["Forrest", "Stewart", "Wilkie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of plant is the Angelica?", "correct_answer": "Herb", "incorrect_answers": ["Tree", "Fern", "Shrub"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character from The Goonies said Scared Mikey?", "correct_answer": "Brand", "incorrect_answers": ["Andy", "Mouth", "Chunk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the words, delivered by Kenickie in the movie Grease: I was lugging boxes at .............. .", "correct_answer": "Bargain City", "incorrect_answers": ["Frosty Palace", "Franks garage", "Five and dime store"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clint Eastwood considered this director his teacher and  dedicated his movie Unforgiven to him.", "correct_answer": "Don Siegel", "incorrect_answers": ["Sam Peckinpah", "Gore Verbinski", "Michael Gondry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Shakespearean comedy inspired Cole Porters musical Kiss Me, Kate?", "correct_answer": "The Taming of the Shrew", "incorrect_answers": ["Measure for Measure", "Twelfth Night", "Alls Well That Ends Well"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Hindu word Krishna mean?", "correct_answer": "dark or dark blue", "incorrect_answers": ["the lord", "daylight", "my lord"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do customers get free when they filled up at Captain Spauldings in the horror film House of 1000 Corpses?", "correct_answer": "Chicken", "incorrect_answers": ["Califlower", "Crisps", "Cheese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Han Solos well known first mate?", "correct_answer": "Chewbacca", "incorrect_answers": ["Princess Leia", "Jabba the Hut", "Luke Skywalker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plant grows wild in the dry, desert ground of Texas and Mexico and is one of the very few spineless varieties among some two thousand different types of cacti growing in the world.", "correct_answer": "Peyote", "incorrect_answers": ["Sorcerers Cherry", "Sunbirch", "Stickletop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This persons goddaughter is Gwyneth Paltrow and he hired her for her first role, Wendy in Hook. Who is he?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Zemeckis", "Brian DePalma", "Ridley Scott"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the title of a song from the Hit TV Series, The Drew Carey Show.\nMoon Over ____", "correct_answer": "Parma", "incorrect_answers": ["Miamisburg", "Shaker Heights", "Pittsburgh"]}]